

ARABINDA JENA

Team Lead – Accounts & Finance 09439414097, 09403917437 Mail ID: arabinda28@gmail.com

15Years & 1 Month of experience in Finance & Accounts, Admin works in Project Management of Construction, Infrastructure & EPC Sector. Include 1Year & 7Months Of Experience in **Manufacturing Industries**

> Accounts & Finance, ADMIN works of

Management & Manufacturing

Working Knowledge

in TALLY Prime, ERP

Deals with Clients

Statutory Bodies.

Team Leadership,

Strong Decision

(Govt/PSU), Labour Commission & other

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

Project

Industries

& SAP.

Experienced and dedicated Team Lead- Accounts & Finance, Admin, bringing forth several years of valuable industry, Projects experience and a commitment to providing a variety of financial and analytical review services to company departments and clients. Adept in ensuring compliance with accounting principles and federal regulations.

Employment History

1. KRYFS POWER COMPONENTS LIMITED, Mumbai

Service Period: 08/2016 To Currently working.

Role- Team Lead –Accounts & Finance, ADMIN.

1. Satyam (FAB) Industries Pvt. Ltd. – Bhoapl, Madhya Pradhesh

Under KRYFS Transformer Division

Manufacturing of Electrical equipment's, Transformer of different types & Fabrication works of Transformer.

(Period 21-July-2021 to Currently Working)

2. Project Name: Deen Dayal Upadhyaya Gram Jyoti Yojana (DDUGJY),

Under South Bihar Power Distribution Company Limited (SBPDCL), working of Separation/Creation of Agriculture / Non Agriculture feeders, Strenthening & Electrification, Conducting (33/11)KV 12Nos. Substations, LT Single Phase service connection in Aurangabad district, Bihar

(Period 24-May-2021 to 30-Nov-2021)

3. Project Name: Restructured Accelerated Power Development and Reforms Program (R-APDRP),

Under Central Electricity Supply Unity of Odisha (CESU)& TATA Project Central Odisha Distribution Limited (TPCODL), Conducting (33/11)KV UG,LT ABCable, HT ABC Cable,250 KV New Transformer Installation, argumentation, Maintenance of Substations & installation of Metering in Cuttack, Odisha

(Period 16-Nov-2016 to 31-Dec-2021)

Communication Address.

Maker.

Teacher's Colony, Bandra Kurla Complex, Mumbai - 400051 Maharashtra

Whatsapp-9403917437

Computer Proficiency PGDCA

Tally Prime

4. Project Name: Odisha Distribution System Strengthening Project (ODSSP) Pakage-01 of Phase -I,

Under Odisha Power Transmission Corporation Limited (OPTCL), Conducting (33/11)KV of 9Nos. Substations in Angul & Dhenkanal district Odisha

(Period 22-Aug-2016 to 15-Nov-2016 & 01- Jan-2020 to Current Date)

JOB RESPONSIBILITY: ¬

- Recording transactions in daily basis in Tally Prime & SAP.
- Cash Handling, Preparation of Cash Book,
- Heading Complete Bank Activities, BRS, Bank Guaranty, Letter of Credit.
- Checking of Purchase Order, Invoices of Vendors & Customers for Payment processing.
- Checking Stock Statement and Valuation of Stock.
- Timely Preparation of Client Erection & Supply RA Bills as per JMC, MVAC, MDCC.
- Timely Preparation & Audit of Subcontractors & Labour suppliers WO, Bills as per work done.
- Checking Workers EPF, ESI, Health Certificate, over time work register, Salary/wages & Bonus Payment.
- Follow of Client Bills for Approval & collections.
- Preparation Of Monthly Financial Statement includes Liability Statement, Fund Flow Statement
- Checking Work –in Progress Report & To ensure all vouchers, debit / Credit slips etc are accounted for.
- Preparation of Yearly & Half yearly Audit reports for external auditors.
- Knowledge in Labour Licence Open, renewals & compliances.
- To ensure timely payments in line with the statutory regulations, Provident Fund, Professional Tax, other
 Statutory Compliance.
- Preparation of Goods and Services Tax filling, TDS & TCS.
- Preparation of Trial Balance, P/L Account and Balance Sheet in Tally Prime.
- Reporting to CFO & Finance manager of Head office.

2. GAMMON INDIA LIMITED, MUMBAI

Service Period- 21/07/2007 To 20/08/2016

Role- Head Accountant (Projects)

- Project Name: Parli New Thermal Power Project Unit- 7 & 8,
 Under Maharashtra State Power Generation Company Limited (250 MW), Parli V. Beed, Maharashtra. (Period 31-Dec-2010 to 20-Aug2016)
- 2. Project Name: Bhusawal Thermal Power Project,

Under TATA Project Limited, Owner Maharashtra State Power Generation Company Limited (500x2 MW), Bhusawal. Jalgaon, Maharashtra (Period 01- Mar-2013 to 20-Aug-2016)

3. Project Name: Shree Singaji Thermal Power Project, Malwa

Under Madhya Pradesh State Power Generation Company Limited. (650x2MW), Mundi, Khandwa, Madhya Pradesh,

(Period 31-Dec- 2009 to 30-Dec-2010)

4. Project Name: Parli Thermal Power Project Unit-6
Under Maharashtra State Power Generation Company Limited (250 MW), Parli V, Beed, Maharashtra (Period 21-July-2007 to 30-Dec-2009)

JOB RESPONSIBILITY

- Recording transactions in daily basis in ERP
- Cash Handling, Preparation of Cash Book, and Completing the Bank Activities,
- Checking of Purchase Order Material Receipt Note, Stock Statement
- Audit vendor Bills and Subcontractor Measurement Book for Payment processing.
- Fund Management, Deployment, Liability Statements
- Timely preparation and updating of all accounting documents
- To ensure timely payments in line with the statutory regulations, Statutory Compliance
- Record Maintain for Taxes, TDS, PTAX.
- Staffs & Workers records, Wages/Salary Sheet preparation,
- Maintain & Project Budget Monitoring, To ensure all vouchers, debit note & credit note slips etc.
- Facilitate Internal Audit at site & Help to internal and external auditors Annually/Half Yearly audit
- To disburse payments (Salary or Wages) to employees and labour & to clear vendor bills on time
- Preparation of Monthly Financial Statement (MFS) and Project Liability Statement.
- Preparation of Billing and Collection Statement from Client.
- Knowledge in Labour Licence Open, renewals & compliances.
- Handle Project Staffs, workers records, Gate pass, Over time works.
- Coordination to client as per requirement for Supply & Erection Bills Approval & Collection
- Preparation of Trial Balance, P/L Account and Balance Sheet in ERP.
- Discussion with Project Head regarding Project Management.

3. Hariyana Traders (Supplier: Goodyear India Ltd.), Jajpur Road, Orissa

Role:- Accountant Cum Computer Operator

Period of Service: Feb 2003 To Aug 2005

Job Responsibility: Preparation of Cash Ledger, Bank Ledger, Preparation of BRS, VAT Maintain in Tally,
Preparation of Monthly Statement, Making Journal Voucher, Party (Debtor/Creditor) Ledger,
Maintain Salary A/c, Customer Service Records, Working with Account Package Tally, Working with Internet.

STUDY PROJECT WORK:

Two Months Study Project Work at "North Eastern Electricity Supply Company Of Orissa Limited" (NESCO), Jajpur Road, Jajpur, Odisha on "WORKING CAPITAL MANAGEMENT". Period of Training: June'06- July'06.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- 1. MBA in Finance from Bijupatnaik University of Technology, Orissa in the Year 2005-2007.
- 2. Graduation in Commerce from Utkal University, Orissa in the Year 1998-2001.
- 3. Higher Secondary in Science from C.H.S.E, Orissa in the year 1996-1998.
- 4. Matriculation from Board of Higher Secondary Education, Orissa in the year 1996

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : Arabinda Jena

Father's Name : Nrusingh Charan Jena

Permanent Address : At/Po – Rachhipur,

Dist – Jajpur, Odisha, Pin-755019

Date of Birth : 3rd April 1981

• Gender : Male

Nationality : Indian

• Language Known : English, Hindi, Oriya.

• Marital Status : Married

Passport : Available

Hobbies : Reading Books & Playing Computer Games

• Strength : Hardworking, Self Confidence.

I DECLARATION I

I do hereby declare that all the information furnished above me are true and correct to the best of my knowledge & belief.

Date: 28.09.2022

Place: Maharashtra Arabinda Jena